<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevHealth</title>
    <description>Because Developers could be healthy</description>
    <link>https://devhealth.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://devhealth.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:33:23 -0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 00:33:23 -0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>My first day of exercises</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yes, it sucks. You are trying to get out of a sedentary life. You go to a gym and starts the running on a 5.0 velocity in the treadmill and look to the side. A woman running in a 10.0 velocity and other guy on 12.0. I was feeling like a vegetable…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;my-first-impressions&quot;&gt;My first impressions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do not make exercises a long time and at 5 minutes, my legs and my calf it was exploding and screaming to me to stop everthing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But ok, it’s my first day. I will not give up! No problem if the people on my side are running at 20 and 6 miles. It will be slow but progressive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lessons-learned&quot;&gt;Lessons learned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before start to run, it’s healthy make some stretching exercises. Another thing is start slowly and increase velocity step by step.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One last tip is ignore the other people around. Focus on your step and listen some music or a podcast (like &lt;a href=&quot;http://devnaestrada.com.br&quot;&gt;devnaestrada.com.br&lt;/a&gt; =D).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;thumbnail&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/IMG_6248.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;me after workout&quot; class=&quot;img-rounded&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;* The guy on the treadmill it is not me, ok? But could be… :/&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 18:50:00 -0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://devhealth.github.io/2016/01/18/my-first-day-of-exercises/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://devhealth.github.io/2016/01/18/my-first-day-of-exercises/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello Manifest</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Say the legend that a chubby developer is more experienced. But, how legend is a legend the time is coming to leave the laziness and start to running and make exercises.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The motivations are varied and probably you already know it, but let’s start to write about the developers routine on this fight against sedentary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to DevHealth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;support&quot;&gt;Support&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are supported from our friends of &lt;a href=&quot;http://devnaestrada.com.br&quot;&gt;DevNaEstrada&lt;/a&gt;, a brazilian podcast from developers to developers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 16:00:00 -0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://devhealth.github.io/2016/01/04/manifest/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://devhealth.github.io/2016/01/04/manifest/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
